Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Motion Pictures
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Videorecordings documenting Yale University, 1966-2008; Accession 2009-A-156
  - 3031: Tercentennial Gala, camera 1, tape 1, from center angle with Jack Ford included, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 948)
  - 3032: Tercentennial Gala, camera 1, tape 2, from center angle with Jack Ford included, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 949)
  - 3033: Tercentennial Gala, camera 2, tape 1, from right side with Jack Ford included, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 950)
  - 3034: Tercentennial Gala, camera 2, tape 2, from right side with Jack Ford included, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 951)
  - 3035: Tercentennial Gala, camera 3, tape 1, from center angle without Jack Ford, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 952)
  - 3036: Tercentennial Gala, live bowl show from center angle without Jack Ford, camera 3, tape 2, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 774)
  - 3037: Tercentennial Gala, live bowl show from various angles, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 775)
  - 3082: B-roll, Tercentennial Select Reel: students on campus, campus shots, classrooms, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 923)
  - 3086: Promo, Exploding Y logo with and without tercentennial title, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 925)
  - 3089: Alumni interviews at Yale 300 / Yale traditions, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 926)
  - 3090: Yale 300th Melt, live event, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 927)
  - 3091: Tercentennial b-roll, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 51)
  - 3094: Campus b-roll, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 54)
  - 3120: Yale Club New York Birthday greetings, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 78)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 78U)
  - 3122: Yale Club of Houston, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 80)
  - 3190: Tercentennial convocation, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 112)
  - 3198: Tercentennial news coverage, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 119)
  - 3209: Tercentennial Convocation with President Levin's Address, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 956)
  - 3210: Yale Tercentennial Convocation, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 129)
  - 3220: Celebrate Yale 300 Alumni interviews, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 138)
  - 3483: Tercentennial symposium closing address, Clinton's address on Cross Campus, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 339)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 339U)
  - 3573: Tercentennial closing address: President Clinton's speech on Cross Campus, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 901)
  - 3941: Tercentennial Bowl Celebration, WTNH, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 587)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 587U)
  - 3943: Tercentennial Bowl Celebration, WVIT, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 919)
  - 4094: Celebrate Yale 300, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 717)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 717U)
  - 4229: Yale 300 Convocation, Cross Campus, 2001 October 5; 1 (Box 830)
  - 3104: William Jefferson Clinton Tercentennial Address, 2001 October 6; 1 (Box 64)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 64U)
  - 3105: Ernesto Zedillo Tercentennial Address, 2001 October 6; 1 (Box 65)
  - 3799: Bill Clinton Speech, 2001 October 6; 1 (Box 499)
  - 3796: Yale Events, 2001 October 7; 1 (Box 496)
  - 3005: Celebrate Yale 300, live event, 2001 October 10; 1 (Box 706)
  - 3040: Open House tape 1, 2001 October 21; 1 (Box 14)
  - 3041: Open House tape 3, 2001 October 21; 1 (Box 15)
  - 3042: Open House tape 4, 2001 October 21; 1 (Box 16)
  - 3016: Yale Tercentennial Bowl Show, highlight, 2001 October 26; 1 (Box 771)
  - 3017: Yale Tercentennial Bowl show, 2001 October 26; 1 (Box 8)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 8U)
  - 3797: Reza Pahlavi, Pierson and Yale lecture newsclips, 2001 October 29; 1 (Box 497)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 497U)
  - 3871: Gilmore Girls: Presenting Lorelei, 2001 November 6; 1 (Box 540)
  - 3978: Titans, 2001 November 14; 1 (Box 614)
  - 3786: Career High School, anatomy class, 2001 November 19; 1 (Box 487)
  - 3006: Celebrate Yale 300 with Gala Weekend, highlight, 2001 December 1; 1 (Box 735)
  - 4096: Celebrate Yale 300, 2001 December 1; 1 (Box 719)
  - 3803: Thunderbird Story, 2001 December 5; 1 (Box 502)
  - 3002: ESPN Pilot Pen, 2002; 1 (Box 3)
  - 3521: Pilot Pen Broadcast, 2002 January 1; 1 (Box 372)
  - 4095: Yale University Tercentennial Gala, 2002 January 10; 1 (Box 718)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 718U)
  - 3805: NYSP / Queen Edwards, 2002 January 17; 1 (Box 504)
  - 3899: Martin Luther King Day Celebrations, 2002 January 21; 1 (Box 552)
  - 3490: American Business Profile: Yale, 2002 January 29; 1 (Box 346)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 346U)
  - 3789: Sandra's, WTNH and WFSB, 2002 January 30; 1 (Box 490)
  - 3812: Sandra's, WFSB, 2002 January 30; 1 (Box 909)
  - 3813: Sandra's, WTNH, 2002 January 30; 1 (Box 910)
  - 3995: Langston Hughes, WTNH, 2002 January 31; 1 (Box 630)
  - 3806: Teacher Prep., 2002 February 3; 1 (Box 505)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 505U)
  - 4006: Yale - Philharmonic, 2002 February 7; 1 (Box 640)
  - 3484: Yale Tercentennial Gala, 2002 February 26; 1 (Box 340)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 340U)
  - 4055: GESO Town Meeting on Unionization, 2002 February 27; 1 (Box 681)
  - 3977: Sports Shots, 2002 February 28; 1 (Box 613)
  - 4302: John Morrell, Segway LLC, Fox 61 WTIC-TV, 2002 March 5; 1 (Box 506)
  - 3948: Yale NIT, 2002 March 20; 1 (Box 592)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 592U)
  - 3954: Robotics, WVIT and WTNH, 2002 April 4; 1 (Box 595)
  - 4213: Thomas C. Duffy 20th Anniversary Tribute, 2002 April 6; 1 (Box 815)
  - 3830: Dr. Ben Carson, 2002 April 13; 1 (Box 521)
  - 3968: Yale Astronomy, News Channel 8 Marketing, 2002 April 17; 1 (Box 605)
  - 3545: Universidad de Yale, 2002 May 1; 1 (Box 387)
  - European business profile
    - 3494: Yale, 2002 May 2; 1 (Box 348)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 348U)
    - 3496: Spanish, 2002 May 2; 1 (Box 896)
    - 3497: French, 2002 May 2; 1 (Box 897)
    - 3498: Profile of Yale Life (German), 2002 May 2; 1 (Box 898)
    - 3499: English, Spanish, Italian, French, German, 2002 May 2; 1 (Box 899)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 899U)
  - 4287: OPA News Archive, 2001 Apr 21-2002 May 26, 1 (Box 216)
  - 3792: Yale Commencement, WTNH, 2002 May 27; 1 (Box 493)
  - 3793: Yale Commencement, WTIC and WVIT, 2002 May 27; 1 (Box 908)
  - 4284: OPA News Archive, 1999 Dec 12-2002 May 27, 1 (Box 186)
  - 3023: Yale Long service awards, 2002 June 6; 1 (Box 111)
  - 3564: Valerie Klowkow on Oprah, 2002 June 7; 1 (Box 405)
  - 3801: Valerie Klokow Segment, Oprah, 2002 June 7; 1 (Box 501)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 501U)
  - 3804: Gus Ranus, 2002 June 11; 1 (Box 503)
  - 3828: Scholar Clips, 2002 July 1; 1 (Box 519)
  - 3930: Prof. Nordhaus, 2002 August 7; 1 (Box 579)
  - 3687: :30 Spot Pilot PEN, ESPN, 2002 August 20; 1 (Box 460)
  - 3860: Sept. 11th One Year Later, 2002 September 1; 1 (Box 529)
  - 3904: 9/11 Arts Discussion, 2002 September 11; 1 (Box 556)
  - 3905: 9/11 Religion Discussion, 2002 September 11; 1 (Box 557)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 557U)
  - 3906: 9/11 Law and Human Rights Discussion, 2002 September 11; 1 (Box 558)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 558U)
  - 3907: 9/11 Geopolitics Discussion, 2002 September 11; 1 (Box 559)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 559U)
  - 3857: Economic Consequences of the Vietnam War, Vietnam environment post-war, 2002 September 13; 1 (Box 528)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 528U)
  - 4301: Yale Eye Center, The Eye Site PSA, Westfield Shoppingtown Meriden and Connecticut Post, 2002 September 13-28; 1 (Box 477)
  - 4225: Kofi Annan Visits Yale World Fellows, 2002 October 2; 1 (Box 826)
  - 3832: Mona Lisa Smiles, 2002 November 1; 1 (Box 522)
  - 3829: Caroline Rhea Show, 2002 November 7; 1 (Box 520)
  - 3867: Gilmore Girls, Let the Games Begin, 2002 November 19; 1 (Box 536)
  - 3814: Whiffs, performance on West Wing, 2002 December 11; 1 (Box 510)
  - 3815: Whiffs, Connecticut News Today, WVIT, 2002 December 11; 1 (Box 912)
  - 3881: West Wing Episode,Whiffenpoofs, 2002 December 11; 1 (Box 546)
  - 3917: Yale Whiffenpoofs on TV, 2002 December 11; 1 (Box 916)
  - 3486: Whiffenpoofs at the White House, 2002 December 12; 1 (Box 342)
  - 3678: TV30 coverage of the Whiffs on West Wing, 2002 December 12; 1 (Box 904)
  - 3974: Timeless: The Yale Bowl, ESPN, 2003; 1 (Box 610)
  - 3822: Yale Student Deaths in Accident on I-95, 2003 January 17; 1 (Box 517)
  - 3692: Yale Student Car Accident on I-95, 2003 January 24; 1 (Box 465)
  - 3821: Press Conference of I-95 Accident, WVIT, 2003 January 24; 1 (Box 516)
  - 3936: Gilder - Lehman Ctr. Lecture, 2003 February 2; 1 (Box 583)
  - 3827: Pfizer, 2003 February 3; 1 (Box 518)
  - 4289: Gary Fryer Lecture: Andrew Heyward, 2003 February 6; 1 (Box 268)
  - 3643: Kyle Burnat Memorial - Battell Chapel, 2003 February 15; 1 (Box 420)
  - 3928: Lehrer News Hour, 2003 February 24; 1 (Box 577)
  - 3644: Jeopardy, 2003 March 1; 1 (Box 421)
  - 3654: Lehrer - The Cost of War, 2003 March 5; 1 (Box 431)
  - 3656: Yale 300: Behind the Ivy, 2003 March 5; 1 (Box 903)
  - 3811: Lehrer News Hour, cost of war, 2003 March 5; 1 (Box 509)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 509U)
  - 3972: Yale Science Fair, 2003 March 11; 1 (Box 609)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 609U)
  - 3695: Smile Study, 2003 March 18; 1 (Box 468)
  - 3646: War in Iraq Teach In, featuring Lust-Okar, Hill, Kennedy, Kagan, 2003 March 26; 1 (Box 423)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 423U)
  - 3927: Iraq War, 2003 March 26; 1 (Box 576)
  - 3914: Discovery Spotlight - Thomas Friedman, 2003 April 1; 1 (Box 564)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 564U)
  - 3956: Iraq: Beyond the Headlines, 2003 April 1; 1 (Box 597)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 597U)
  - 3647: The Iraq War and the Media, 2003 April 3; 1 (Box 424)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 424U)
  - 3649: Forum on the Iraq War, featuring Ackerman, Apaduri, Gilroy, Kern, Thomas, 2003 April 4; 1 (Box 426)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 426U)
  - 3853: Economic Costs of the Iraq War, American foreign policy and economics debate, 2003 April 6; 1 (Box 527)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 527U)
  - 3648: The War and its Repercussions, featuring G. Smith, Gaddis, Kagan, Ranus, S. Smith, 2003 April 10; 1 (Box 425)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 425U)
  - 4207: Rick Levin 10-Year Party 1, 2003 April 11; 1 (Box 809)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 809U)
  - 4208: Rick Levin 10-Year Party 2, 2003 April 11; 1 (Box 810)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 810U)
  - 3652: The Future of the United Nations, featuring Kennedy, Hill, Sutterlin, 2003 April 13; 1 (Box 429)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 429U)
  - 3875: Gilmore Girls, Yale acceptance episode, 2003 April 15; 1 (Box 544)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 544U)
  - 3818: WVIT in New Haven, 2003 April 17; 1 (Box 513)
  - 3851: Iraq War Debate: American Foreign Policy, 2003 April 17; 1 (Box 526)
  - 3866: Gilmore Girls: Happy Birthday Baby, 2003 April 22; 1 (Box 535)
  - 3833: The War in Iraq: Nation Building, 2003 April 24; 1 (Box 523)
  - 3820: Yale Student Accident, WTNH, 2003 April 25; 1 (Box 514)
  - 3844: What's the Future: War in Iraq teach-in, 2003 April 27; 1 (Box 525)
  - 4132: RCL: Celebrating the First Ten Years, 2003 April 28; 1 (Box 749)
    - Use Copy, 2003 April 28; 1 (Box 749U)
  - 3933: Yale and Unions, 2003 April 30; 1 (Box 582)
    - Use copy, 2003 April 30; 1 (Box 582U)
  - 3651: The War in Iraq: Open Discussion with Yale Students, 2003 May 4; 1 (Box 428)
    - Use copy, 2003 May 4; 1 (Box 428U)
  - 3840: The War in Iraq: Student Discussion, 2003 May 4; 1 (Box 515)
  - 3898: Yale - War Debate; NBC News coverage, 2003 May 4; 1 (Box 551)
  - 3873: Gilmore Girls: Those are Strings, Pinnocchio, 2003 May 20; 1 (Box 542)
  - 3696: Ryan Martin Spot - Today Show, 2003 May 27; 1 (Box 469)
    - Use copy, 2003 May 27; 1 (Box 469U)
  - 3971: NBC Today Show: Gangel Ryan Martin, 2003 May 27; 1 (Box 608)
  - 3931: Nightline, 2003 May 29; 1 (Box 580)
  - 3982: Gates / Beinecke, 2003 May 30; 1 (Box 618)
    - Use copy, 2003 May 30; 1 (Box 618U)
  - 3688: Richard Levin's Opening Remarks, 2003 May 31; 1 (Box 461)
  - 3979: Titans of Cancer Research, 2003 June 1; 1 (Box 615)
  - 3986: Yale- NH Teachers Institute, WTNH, 2003 June 20; 1 (Box 621)
  - 4285: OPA News Archive, May 27, 2002-June 21, 2003, 2003 June 21; 1 (Box 188)
  - 4286: OPA Archive, June 23, 2003 -, 2003 June 23; 1 (Box 198)
  - 4021: Block tapes of news, Channel 30, 2003 June 25; 1 (Box 915)
  - 3965: Rose Community Center / YPD (New police station being built), 2003 June 30; 1 (Box 602)
  - 3981: Louis Daniels, WNBC-TV4, New York City, 2003 July 14; 1 (Box 617)
    - Use copy, 2003 July 14; 1 (Box 617U)
  - 4290: This is Jeopardy, 2003 August 12; 1 (Box 280)
  - 4018: Block Taping of News - WTNH: Preserving books in Law School Library, 2003 August 19; 1 (Box 646)
  - 4019: Block Taping of News - WFSB/CNN: Preserving books in Law School Library, 2003 August 19; 1 (Box 647)
  - 3872: Gilmore Girls: Ballrooms and Biscotti, 2003 September 23; 1 (Box 541)
  - 3925: Sarah Levin, 2003 October 7; 1 (Box 574)
  - 3239: Poynter Lecture - Elisabeth Rosenthal, 2003 October 18; 1 (Box 152)
  - 3800: The Life of Henri Nouwen, 2003 November 1; 1 (Box 500)
  - 3919: Donald Kagan on BookTV, 2003 November 3; 1 (Box 568)
  - 3861: Jeopardy, 2003 November 10-11; 1 (Box 530)
  - 3862: Jeopardy, 2003 November 12; 1 (Box 531)
  - 3863: Jeopardy, 2003 November 13-14; 1 (Box 532)
  - 4004: Main St., CTPTV, 2003 November 14; 1 (Box 638)
  - 4005: Organic Farm, 2003 November 14; 1 (Box 639)
  - 3864: Jeopardy, 2003 November 17; 1 (Box 533)
  - 3865: Jeopardy, 2003 November 18-19; 1 (Box 534)
  - 3645: Jeopardy #9/#10, 2003 November 20-21; 1 (Box 422)
  - 3653: 60 Minutes - Jeopardy, 2003 November 23; 1 (Box 430)
  - 4007: Special Report, interview with Robert Rubin, 2003 November 24; 1 (Box 641)
  - 3256: Poynter Lecture, Elisabeth Bumiller, 2003 December 3; 1 (Box 168)
  - 4053: G.E. News Conference - China, 2003 December 8; 1 (Box 679)
  - 3970: CBS Morning Show, 2004 January 11; 1 (Box 607)
  - 3874: Gilmore Girls, 2004 January 20; 1 (Box 543)
  - 4246: A Conversation in One Brief Afternoon, Richard Broadhead, Duke University Studios, 2004 February 1; 1 (Box 839)
  - 3924: Levin Commision Appointment, 2004 February 6; 1 (Box 573)
  - 4034: Poynter Lecture - Helene Cooper, 2004 February 11; 1 (Box 659)
  - 3988: Anderson Cooper, CNN, 2004 February 20; 1 (Box 623)
  - 3923: Naomi Wolf, 2004 February 23; 1 (Box 572)
  - 4288: News Channel 30 (NBC): Marc Polenza, 2004 March 12; 1 (Box 239)
  - 4294: ESPN Timeless: Yale Bowl, 2004 March 18; 1 (Box 351)
  - 4032: Brown vs. Board of Ed Conference at Yale, 2004 April 3; 1 (Box 657)
  - 4128: Fox News Channel, coverage of Pope John Paul II, 2004 April 3; 1 (Box 746)
  - 4031: Poynter Lecture - Margaret Warner, 2004 April 12; 1 (Box 656)
  - 4033: Poynter Lecture - David Ignatius, 2004 April 26; 1 (Box 658)
  - 4058: Bush, Kerry and Yale, 2004 April 28; 1 (Box 684)
  - 4056: Hamburger Month, 2004 May 7; 1 (Box 682)
  - 4209: Dean Richard Brodhead Farewell Reception, 2004 May 18; 1 (Box 811)
  - 4300: Kimberly Yonkers - Professor of Psychiatry, 2004 May 18; 1 (Box 452)
  - 4042: Yale Commencement 2004, 2004 May 24; 1 (Box 669)
  - 4051: Perlman in Shanghai, 2004 June 8; 1 (Box 677)
  - 4182: CBS Sunday Morning - Cole Porter, 2004 July 4; 1 (Box 795)
  - 4044: Mayor's Office - Live From the Rock, West Haven, CT, 2004 August 1; 1 (Box 671)
  - 4045: Womens Soccer: 2004 Olympics, 2004 August 11; 1 (Box 672)
  - 4046: 2004 Olympics Opening Ceremonies, 2004 August 13; 1 (Box 673)
  - 4035: Yale China Delegation Orientation, 2004 August 14; 1 (Box 660)
  - 4036: U.S. Research University Levin, Lorimer, 2004 August 15; 1 (Box 661)
  - 4037: Building a World-Class Faculty I, 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 662)
  - 4037: Building a World-Class Faculty II, 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 663)
  - 4039: Ways to Compensate and Motivate Faculty I, 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 665)
  - 4039: Ways to Compensate and Motivate Faculty II, 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 666)
  - 4047: Swimming: 2004 Olympics, 2004 August 16; 1; Video tape tracking calibration errors throughout the original tape. (Box 674)
  - 4062: Y-China Adv. Univ. Leadership Prog., 2004 August 16; 1 (Box 688)
  - 4188: Yale-China: Penny Laurans, 2004 August 17; 1 (Box 799)
  - 4189: Yale-China: Richard Levin, 2004 August 17; 1 (Box 800)
  - 4190: Yale-China: Peter Salovey, Panel, 2004 August 17; 1 (Box 801)
  - 4191: Yale-China: Phil Long, 2004 August 17; 1 (Box 802)
  - 4075: 2004 Summer Olympics/Athens, 2004 August 17-18; 1 (Box 697)
  - 4040: Building World Class Research Enterprise, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 667)
  - 4049: Rowing: 2004 Olympics, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 675)
  - 4050: Swimming, Judo, Sailing: 2004 Olympics, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 676)
  - 4192: Yale-China: Library Presentation, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 803)
  - 4193: Yale-China: William Bowen, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 804)
  - 4194: Yale-China: Hockfield, Hamilton, Xu, 2004 August 18; 1 (Box 805)
  - 4041: Leadership Development, 2004 August 19; 1 (Box 668)
  - 4195: Yale-China: Jeff Sonnenfeld, 2004 August 19; 1 (Box 806)
  - 4196: Yale-China: Robert Sternberg, 2004 August 19; 1 (Box 807)
  - 4197: Yale-China: Sonnenfeld, Vroom, 2004 August 19; 1 (Box 808)
  - 4066: Y-China Adv. Univ. Leadership Prog., 2004 August 23; 1 (Box 692)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 692U)
  - 4063: Y-China Adv. Univ. Leadership Prog., 2004 August 24; 1 (Box 689)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 689U)
  - 4065: Y-China Adv. Univ. Leadership Prog., 2004 August 25; 1 (Box 691)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 691U)
  - 4052: NHK Japan - Levin, 2004 September 1; 1 (Box 678)
  - 4029: Charlie Rose/Roland Betts, 2004 September 15; 1; Audio distorted on original recording. (Box 654)
  - 4038: Yellow in a White World, 2004 September 27; 1 (Box 664)
  - 4043: Gilmore Girls, Branford College, 2004 October 5; 1 (Box 670)
  - 4030: The Daily Show (with Jon Stewart), Fareed Zakaria, 2004 October 20; 1 (Box 655)
  - 4027: Charlie Rose/President Levin, 2004 October 22; 1 (Box 652)
  - 4073: Charlie Rose: Gordon / Levin, 2004 October 22; 1 (Box 695)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 695U)
  - 4082: Jane Pauly/Today Show: Whiffenpoofs, 2004 October 25; 1 (Box 704)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 704U)
  - 4054: Poynter Lecture - Judy Woodruff, 2004 November 15; 1 (Box 680)
  - 4254: VOA: America's Global College Forum, Yale College student Ben Dineen (Ireland), 2004 December 7; 1 (Box 846)
  - 4074: SEIU-Union Ads, 2005 January 19; 1 (Box 696)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 696U)
  - 4256: VOA: America's Global College Forum, Yale College Student Cesar Moran (Peru), 2005 January 25; 1 (Box 848)
  - 4078: Law School Military Recruitment, 2005 February 2; 1 (Box 700)
  - 4255: VOA: America's Global College Forum, Yale College Student Ruramisai Charumbira (Zimbabwe), 2005 February 8; 1 (Box 847)
  - 4079: Poynter Lecture - Michael Wilbon, 2005 February 23; 1 (Box 701)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 701U)
  - 4137: Poynter Lecture, 2005 February 23; 1 (Box 754)
  - 4072: Tracking the Global Warming Debate, 2005 March 27; 1 (Box 694)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 694U)
  - 4061: Poynter Lecture - David Brooks, 2005 March 29; 1 (Box 687)
  - 4081: Richard Levin/Intelligence Report, 2005 April 1; 1 (Box 703)
  - 4242: Fox and Friends: R. Levin Intelligence Commission Report, 2005 April 1; 1 (Box 835)
  - 4077: Thirteen: News Hour With Jim Lehrer, 2005 April 22; 1 (Box 699)
  - 4076: CSPAN: Intellectual Property Comm., 2005 April 25; 1 (Box 698)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 698U)
  - 4127: Yale University Story, Channel One Russia, 2005 May 1; 1 (Box 745)
  - 4308: Mark D'Antonio - YNH Hospital, 2005 May 4; 1 (Box 561)
  - 3962: West Wing, 2005 May 14; 1 (Box 599)
  - 4243: All Things Considered, Walter Gilliam, 2005 May 17; 1 (Box 836)
  - 4309: Walter Gilliam - Yale Child Study Center, 2005 May 17; 1 (Box 566)
  - 4310: Dr. Alan Kazdin - Director of Yale Child Conduct Clinic, 2005 May 18; 1 (Box 567)
  - 4080: Good Morning America, 2005 May 24; 1 (Box 702)
  - 4083: Thirteen: News Hour With Jim Lehrer, Women in Science, 2005 June 1; 1 (Box 705)
  - 4124: News Channel 8: Urban Teachers, 2005 June 14; 1 (Box 742)
  - 4129: Fox 5 News at 5, 2005 June 14; 1 (Box 747)
  - 4125: News Hour with Jim Lehrer, Nayan Chanda, 2005 June 21; 1 (Box 743)
  - 4131: CBS Weekend Journal, Jeffrey Garten, 2005 July 17; 1 (Box 748)
  - 4126: News Hour with Jim Lehrer, Dr. Eugene Redmond/Stem Cells, 2005 August 16; 1 (Box 744)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 744U)
  - 4247: News 13 News This Morning: Tilly Philbrick, Diabetic, WLOS-TV, 2005 August 29; 1 (Box 840)
  - 4234: Dikembe Mutombo/Yale Tour, WTNH-TV, 2005 September 21; 1 (Box 833)
  - 4337: Dr. Hilary Blumberg, 2005 November 9; 1 (Box 822)
  - 4245: NBC News, Channel 30, 2005 November 10; 1 (Box 838)
  - 4315: Dr. Karl Yaggi - Professor of Medicine, 2005 November 10; 1 (Box 589)
  - 4283: Destination: New England, The Travel Channel, 2005 November 22; 1 (Box 175)
  - 4121: Inside Edition, Sayed Rahmatullah Hashemi, 2006 March 3; 1 (Box 739)
  - 4119: Al Jazeera Washington, Interview with Zhiwu Chen, 2006 April 20; 1 (Box 737)
  - 4336: Dr. Edward Chu, 2006 May 24; 1 (Box 821)
  - 4272: Good Morning America: Mercado Global, 2006 August 11; 1 (Box 857)
  - 4123: President Levin Interview, 2006 September 14; 1 (Box 741)
  - 4248: Yale and President Levin TV Spot, 2006 September 14; 1 (Box 841)
  - 4270: Chen Zhili meets with Yale President, CCTV, 2006 November 13; 1 (Box 855)
  - 4271: Power Lunch (CNBC): Ivy Alexander, 2006 November 17; 1 (Box 856)
  - 4274: Iran - The Most Dangerous Nation, Koppel on Discovery, 2006 November 21; 1 (Box 859)
  - 4276: MSNBC: Levin Lays Wreath at Ford's Casket, 2007 January 2; 1 (Box 861)
  - 4269: The Magic Flute, PBS Great Performances, 2007 January 24; 1 (Box 854)
  - 4109: NHK Japanese News Coverage, Yale, Japan and the World conference, 2007 March 1; 1 (Box 736)
  - 4252: New Peru: Maya Revelations, History Channel, 2007 May 7; 1 (Box 845)
  - 4329: Charlie Rose: "Florian Henckel von Donnersmarck", WNET, 2007 May 18; 1 (Box 755)
  - 4295: CBS Sports: "Science of Golf", 2007 June 24; 1 (Box 368)
  - 4333: Yale and Sustainable Agriculture, WFSB-TV, 2007 September 20; 1 (Box 818)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 818U)
  - 4330: Women and Global Leadership, CNBC India, 2007 October 14; 1 (Box 817)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 817U)
  - 4305: Dr. Fred Volkmar - Yale Child Study Center, 2008 February 23; 1 (Box 548)
  - 4319: Tony Blair Faith Foundation, Dreyfuss ICG, 2008 March 30; 1 (Box 693)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 693U)
  - 4321: Yale Governors Conference, Signing Ceremony and Keynote, 2008 April 18; 1 (Box 710)
  - 4322: Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger, Yale Governors Conference Keynote", 2008 April 18; 1 (Box 721)
  - 4335: Yale Student: Dara Lind, Jeopardy, 2008 May 7; 1 (Box 820)
  - 4316: Beijing Summer Olympics - Part 1, 2008 August 8; 1 (Box 594)
  - 4317: Beijing Summer Olympics - Part 2, 2008 August 8; 1 (Box 619)
  - 4318: Beijing Summer Olympics - Part 3, 2008 August 8; 1 (Box 634)
  - 3964: Claudia and Teacher, 2002 November 2; 1 (Box 601)
  - 3886: Handsome Dan Mascot Shots, ? September 28; 1 (Box 960)
  - 3694: Early Show 7-9am, 9/20/?; 1 (Box 467)
  - Unidentified, undated; 1 (Box 968)
  - 3004: Light Blue: The Lighter Side of Yale, live event, undated; 1 (Box 89)
  - 3013: Vox et Musica Lux et Veritas, undated; 1 (Box 7)
  - 3014: B-roll, Yale Compilation Tape 1: Campus Shots, Sporting Events, Freshman Bazaar, undated; 1 (Box 769)
  - 3015: Yale 300th Show, highlight, undated; 1 (Box 770)
  - 3020: Yale B-roll: Building Close Ups, Class Room Shots, undated; 1 (Box 773)
  - 3021: Yale B-roll, undated; 1 (Box 9)
  - 3022: Yale B-roll compilation, undated; 1 (Box 10)
  - 3024: International Travel Review Yale University, undated; 1 (Box 12)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 12U)
  - 3025: Yale and Public Service, undated; 1 (Box 13)
  - 3025: Yale and Public Service, undated; 1 (Box 867)
  - 3039: Art for Yale: The Real Stuff, highlight, undated; 1 (Box 849)
  - 3056: Yale Preaching Series tape 1, undated; 1 (Box 27)
  - 3057: Yale Preaching Series tape 2, undated; 1 (Box 28)
  - 3080: Yale Bumps, historic documentary on Yale student life during the 1950's, undated; 1 (Box 922)
  - 3081: Highlight Yale Bumps 300, 1938 football highlights, undated; 1 (Box 46)
  - 3083: Yale Bumps tape #1: famous alumni, Yale Club Alaska birthday wishes, undated; 1 (Box 47)